{
    "subject": "resource/Josh_Homme",
    "predicate": "property/genre",
    "object": "resource/Heavy_metal_music",
    "human_readable": "Josh Homme's genre is Heavy metal music.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9868818521499634,
            "question": "Is Heavy metal music a genre associated with Josh Homme?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9733180999755859,
            "question": "Is Heavy metal a significant part of Josh Homme's musical career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7908696532249451,
            "question": "What genre of music is Josh Homme known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.73001629114151,
            "question": "To which music genre does Josh Homme belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6665213108062744,
            "question": "What type of music does Josh Homme produce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6637660264968872,
            "question": "What musical style does Josh Homme primarily perform in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6024080514907837,
            "question": "Which genre best describes the music created by Josh Homme?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5704506635665894,
            "question": "What kind of music is Josh Homme famous for playing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5502200722694397,
            "question": "What is the primary musical style associated with Josh Homme?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5037060379981995,
            "question": "In what musical subgenre does Josh Homme's work fall?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Josh Homme's genre is Heavy metal music.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7871_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary musical style associated with Josh Homme?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7871_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of music is Josh Homme famous for playing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7871_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which genre best describes the music created by Josh Homme?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7871_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7871_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7871_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7871_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7871_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7871_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7871_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7871_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7871_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7871_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7871_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nWhile the documents mention that Josh Homme's music is \"heavy\" and has elements of stoner rock and metal, they also emphasize his influences from punk and hardcore.  It's more accurate to describe his genre as alternative rock, hard rock, or stoner rock rather than strictly heavy metal. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while Josh Homme is associated with heavy, groove-laden sound and stoner rock and stoner metal (see file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7871/re-ranker-msmarco/10.txt), his music often draws comparisons to metal acts but he has consistently cited punk and hardcore as their primary inspirations (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7871/re-ranker-msmarco/54.txt). Therefore, it is not accurate to say that Josh Homme's genre is solely Heavy metal music."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Josh Homme is associated with genres such as hard rock, stoner rock, and alternative rock. They do not specifically state that his primary genre is heavy metal music. Therefore, the given statement is not supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}